

Mandarin | English

# Raphael Pang Teng Xuan

www.raphaelpang.com

tengxuanp@hotmail.com (+60)11-10696958 Malaysian

Hi, I am a 25 year old IT officer/web dev enthusiast with junior level experience as a software developer.

<u>I am looking for Front End developing / UI-UX</u> <u>designing opportunities</u> to sharpen up my web development skills while do my best to help companies to reach their goals.

### **Work Experience**

#### Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd. (2021 - 2022)

IT Assistant Engineer (April 2021 - April 2022)

- IT system maintenance Server backups, user domain/email account management, server & VMs configuration.
- Desktop support Assist organization's staff by troubleshooting errors regarding hardware, software, system issues.

**Supervisor:** IT Supervisor, Mr. Roger Huang Guan Hao (+60)11-51341316

#### OCK Setia Engineering Sdn. Bhd. (2020)

Software Developer (May 2020 - Dec 2020) Intern (Jan 2020 - May 2020)

- Design & develop new system modules & enhance existing system modules for the company's ERP system.
- Maintain organization's websites.

Supervisor: IT Senior Manager, Ms. Quek Meow Wah

### **Education Level**

#### **Bachelor of Information Systems (2017-2020)**

School of Computing & Creative Media, UOW Malaysia KDU University College

### Key Skills

#### **Graphical Design & UI Design**

Photoshop | Illustrator | Figma | InDesign

#### **Scripting & Programming**

Tailwind CSS | Javascript | React JS | PHP

## **Certificates & Recognitions**

Advance Employee Year 2021

Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.

ISO 27001:2013 Awareness,
Implementation & Internal
Auditing Training

Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.